Right love. Wrong time.
Love, Rosie is a romance, drama, comedy film directed by Christian Ditter.
Since the moment they met at age 5, Rosie and Alex have been best
friends, facing the highs and lows of growing up side by side.
A fleeting shared moment, one missed opportunity, and the decisions that
follow send their lives in completely different directions.
As each navigates the complexities of life, love, and everything in between, they always find
their way back to each other - but is it just friendship, or something more?
Rosie Dunne, played by Lily Collins.
Alex Stewart, played by Sam Claflin.
Greg, played by Christian Cooke.
Sally, played by Tamsin Egerton.
Bethany Williams, played by Suki Waterhouse.
Ruby, played by Jaime Winstone.
Love, Rosie is a 2014 romantic comedy-drama film directed by Christian Ditter from a screenplay by
Juliette Towhidi, based on the 2004 novel Where Rainbows End by Irish author Cecelia Ahern.
It stars Lily Collins and Sam Claflin as two childhood best friends turned lovers who
are separated by circumstances following their high school graduation.
Christian Cooke, Tamsin Egerton, Suki Waterhouse, Jamie Beamish
and Jaime Winstone also appear in supporting roles.
The film addresses themes such as teen pregnancy, adoption, grief and adultery.
Love, Rosie had its world premiere in London on 6 October 2014,
before its theatrical release on 22 October 2014.
Though the film was received poorly by critics, it garnered positive
reviews from audiences and grossed $25.5 million worldwide.
Collins' performance was singled out for praise by both critics and audiences.
The film explores themes of friendship, based on novel or
book, love, best friend, valentine's day.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.